(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) The kids are at a water park for
a field trip.
It is time to go on the water
slide.
Hector is scared to go on the slide.
He looks up and sees how high the
slide is.
Afraid of heights, he does not want to
go on.
He sees all the other kids having fun
on the slide.
Hector gets very upset.
The teacher goes up to talk to him.
She explains to him that it is safe
and nothing will happen.
Hector decides to take the risk.
He climbs up the slide.
He takes a pause before he goes down.
As he goes down, he screams.
At the bottom, he realizes it is not
so bad.
He is now ready to line up and
go again.